Craig Seymour Collection, 1968-2006 SC 144
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 5. Audiovisual (excluding interviews)
  - 5.2. Commercial media, Nearly 1,000 CDs of commercially released audio is included in this collection. The CDs are a mixture of published and unpublished releases. The unpublished releases are primarily promotional copies sent out in advance of an album release for review. The unpublished record
    - Show You How To Do This [DJ Mix] // KeyZ; Big Mike, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3983
    - Inventing The Remix pt. 8 [DJ Mix] // KeyZ; DJ Finesse, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3984
    - Spring Fever 2004 [DJ Mix] // DJ Finesse, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3985
    - Rn'B Takeover 2K5 [DJ Mix] // DJ Finesse, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3986
      Underground Artist
    - Hev, E Components pt. 1 [DJ Mix] // DJ Clue (Rapper), 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3987
    - Hev, E. Components, NBA Finals 2001 pt.4 [DJ Mix] // DJ Clue (Rapper), 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3988
    - Stadium Series pt.4 "A-Street" Holiday Hold-up 2001-2002 [DJ Mix] // DJ Clue (Rapper), 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3989
    - I'm A Show You How To Do This pt. 1 [DJ Mix] // DJ Clue (Rapper), 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3990
    - Special Delivery pt. II [DJ Mix] // Funkmaster Flex (Musician), 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3991
    - Special Delivery pt.III [DJ Mix] // Funkmaster Flex (Musician), 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3992
    - Big Truck Series pt. 3 The D Block Edition "Taking You Out The Game" [DJ Mix] // Funkmaster Flex (Musician), 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3993
    - The Neptunes Present Star Trak [DJ Mix] // DJ Enuff, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3994
    - The Donferquan Show [DJ Mix] // DJ Rhude; Kingz Nation, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3995
    - Rewind: Electro Funk Breakdown [DJ Mix] // Afrika Bambaataa, 1960-, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3996
      DMC
      7930185504-2
    - Young Fly and Flashy [DJ Mix] // Dupri, Jermaine, 1972-, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3997
    - Contagious Killer Cuts Complilation vol. 1 [DJ Mix] // Terry, Todd, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3998
      Contagious
      MDT-8938
    - Queen of the Damned [DJ Mix] // DJ L; Rah Digga, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3999
      Open lock
    - The Return of Bad Boy [DJ Mix] // DJ E. Nyce, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4000
    - Ice Cream (Best of Pharell) [DJ Mix] // DJ Wats, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4001
      Guttamuzic
    - F-Sction Live: Another Classic Here to Stay [DJ Mix] // F-Action, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4002
    - Hot in Here pt. 5 [DJ Mix] // DJ Vlad, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4003
    - Red Heat [DJ Mix] // Tapemasters INC., 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4004
    - The pulling String [DJ Mix] // Ben-Ari, Miri, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4005
    - Fire Blends pt.7 Best of Jay-Z [DJ Mix] // DJ Roli Fingaz, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4006
    - Summer Heat R&B Blendz pt. 20 [DJ Mix] // DJ Doitall, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4007
      Nocturnal
    - Changing Lanes [DJ Mix] // Chops (Rapper); West, Kanye, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4008
      Vocabre
    - Miss Mary J Blige [DJ Mix] // J-Love, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4009
      Street Funk
    - Best of Little Kim [DJ Mix] // DJ 4our5, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4010
    - Untouchables Presents Welcome to Cashville [DJ Mix] // Mixtapemob, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4011
    - Rhythm and Streets pt. 6 [DJ Mix] // DJ Sense, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4012
      Aphilliates
    - DJ GQ pt. 15 [DJ Mix] // DJ GQ, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4013
    - Satisfaction Guaranteed pt.2 [DJ Mix] // DJ L The Masterkey, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4014
      Open Lock
    - New New York: The Movement [DJ Mix] // Tru-Life, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4015
      Ghetto Inmates
    - Hard: Mixtape sampler [DJ Mix] // Jagged Edge, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4016
    - Phonography: The Blue Note Remix-Mix [DJ Mix] // DJ Smash, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4017
      7243 5 26816 2 4V
    - Ignorant Shiiiiit [DJ Mix] // Sickamore; DJ Neptune, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4018
    - Warriors [DJ Mix] // DJ Dirty Harry, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4019
    - Dirty Luv vol.1 [Dj Mix] // DJ Dirty Harry, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4020
    - Jay Exclusive Radio Says [Dj Mix] // JX, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4021
    - The Chef vs. The Butcher // Chops (Rapper); Raekwon (Musician), 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4022
    - R&B Life 17 [DJ Mix] // Action Pac, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4023
    - The: Indicment The: Trial The: Verdict [DJ Mix] // DJ Drama; The P$C, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4024
    - Street Wars III: The Battles for the Streets [DJ Mix] // Pcutta, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4025
    - White Chicks Like Mixtapes too [Dj Mix] // Sparks, Clinton; Wayans Bros., 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4026
    - Subliminal Sessions two [DJ Mix] // Romero, Harry "Choo Choo", 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4027
      [missing disc 1]
    - R&B vol. 23 [DJ Mix] // DJ Famous, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4028
    - R&B vol. 33 [DJ Mix] // DJ Famous, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 4029
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 15 [DJ Mix] // Tony Touch, 2000; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4030
      CSP015-D1/D2
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 16 [DJ Mix] // DJ Muggs, 2000; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4031
      CSP016-D1/D2
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 18 [DJ Mix] // DJ Chill; DJ Nasty, 2000; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4032
      CSP018-D1/D2
    - Cornerstane Mixtape 21 [DJ Mix] // Baby Jane; Hi-Tek, 2000; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4033
      CSP021-D1/D2
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 22 [DJ Mix] // DJ A. Vee; DJ Khaled, 2000; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4034
      CSP022-D1/D2
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 23 [DJ Mix] // Cipha Sounds; DJ Fashen, 2000; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4035
      CSP023-D1/D2
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 24 [DJ Mix] // DJ Bee; Still Will; Touch Tone; DJ Green Lantern, 2000; 3 Audio Discs
      CD 4036
      CSP024-D1/D2/D3
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 27 [DJ Mix] // DJ Slyed; Chubby Chubb, 2001; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4037
      CSP027-D1/D2
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 29 [DJ Mix] // Doo-Wop; DJ Vice, 2001; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4038
      CSP029-D1/D2
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 30 [DJ Mix] // DJ Law; Big B, 2001; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4039
      CSP030-D1/D2
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 31 [DJ Mix] // Roy Barboza; The Dilated Junky DJ Babu, 2001; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4040
      CSP031-D1/D2
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 32/ Training Day Mix [DJ Mix] // DJ Premier; DJ Ran; DJ Green Lantern, 2001; 3 Audio Discs
      CD 4041
      CSP032-D1/D2/D3
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 33- Ladies Edition [DJ Mix] // Cocoa Chanelle; Ji Ji Sweet; K Swift, 2001; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4042
      CSP033-D1/D2
    - Vinyl Wars Part 1 [Cornerstone Mixtape 19]: Attack of The Crate Diggaz [DJ Mix] // DJ Green Lantern, 2000; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4043
      CSP019-D1/D2
    - Cornerstone Mixtape 20 [DJ Mix] // DJ Revolution; DJ Quicksilver, 2000; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4044
      CSP020-D1/D2
    - Subliminal Sessions One [DJ Mix] // Morillo, Erick, 2001; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 4045
      Subliminal
    - Subliminal Sessions Three [DJ Mix] // Morillo, Erick, 2002; 3 Audio Discs
      CD 4046
    - Cornerstone Mixtape: best of 99 [DJ Mix] // DJ Green Lantern; Mr. Choc; Supadupe; DJ Spinbad, 1999; 3 Audio Discs
      CD 4047
      CSP013-D1/D2/D3
    - Reprazent "Dirty Beat" (Remixes) // Roni Size, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6909
      CD-R
      TalkinLoud
    - Freeworld Compilation, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6910
      Freeworld Entertainment
    - The Unofficial 9th Wonder Instrumental Collection, 4 Audio Discs
      CD 6911
      E-NYCE
    - MuzikClub Classics, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6912
      Muzik
      Muzik SI 99/3
    - The Summer Sound System 2002 // Little Louie' Vega, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6913
    - Get R: The C.Ronson Mixtape // Ronson, Mark; Ronson, Samantha, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6914
    - Swords // Leftfield, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6915
      Sony Music Entertainment
      HANDO59CD2
    - Extensions // Elements of Life; Louie Vega, 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6916
      Vega Records
      02VEG02
    - Aline in Wonderland, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6917
      SMALL (Sony Music Associated & Liscensed Labels)
      LC 3025
    - The Cornerstone Player 015, 2 Audio Discs
      CD 6918
      Cornerstone Productions
      CSAP015
    - The Cornerstone Player 014, 2 Audio Discs
      CD 6919
      Press Release
      CSAP014
    - The Cornerstone Player 010, 2 Audio Discs
      CD 6920
      CSAP010
    - After the Playboy Mansion // Dimitri from Paris, 2002; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 6921
      Labels / Virgin France
    - Roger Sanchez Presents Transatlantic Soul Release Yo Self // Terry, Todd, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6922
      Destruction
      LC 8280
    - Heroes! Rewind!, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6923
    - The Compilation Vol. 2 // MAW, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6924
      Maw Records
    - Mixed Up in the Hauge Vol. 1, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6925
      Panama Records
      PAN001
    - Hooligan House: The Sound of 2003 // Audio Bullys, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6926
    - Breaking News: Tony Touch Gets Deeper House Mix #35 // Tony Touch, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6927
    - MicMac House Dance Party, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6928
      Mic Mac
      MIC 91409
    - Rock & Roll // Jungle Sky, 1998; 2 Audio Discs
      CD 6929
      Liquid Sky Music
      JS130
    - Drum & Bass Anthems // Addiction, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6930
      IPC Media
    - Best of 2002, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6931
    - 50 Big Tunes 2013, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6932
      Mixmag
      MM 047
    - Divas Volume 3, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6933
      Strictly Rhythm
      SRDJEP3
    - Drama!: The Unreleased White Labels #24, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6934
      Unreleased White Labels
    - Asphodelic, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 6935
      Asphodel
      ASPH 0991P
    - F-Action 40 // OG Ron C, 2005; 4 Audio Discs
      CD 6936
      BCD Music Group
    - Columbia Records Present: Young Soul Power II // Various Artists (Alica Keys, Blaque, Jo Jo Robinson, Cassie), 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12407
      Promotional Copy
      Columbia Records
      4SK 41585
    - J Records Urban Music Sampler Vol. 2 // Various Artists (Monica, Lyric, Flipmode Squad, Yung Wun, Deborah Cox, Joi Campbell, Tyrese, Shells, Lamya), 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12408
      J1DJ-21208-2
    - So Stylistic // FannyPack, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12409
      TB-1567-2A
    - "Never Enough" -12'' // Lamya, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12410
      CD-R Promotional Copy
    - "Up & Down (In & Out)" // Deborah Cox, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12411
    - Rhapsodies In Black: Music and Words from the Harlem Renaissance Disc One: Struttin' & Stridin' // Various Artists ( Langston Hughes, Duke Ellington, James P. Johnson,Bert Williams, Wally "Famous" Amos, Ethel Waters, Eubie Blake,Mamie Smith, Branford Marsalis, Ida Cox, Clarence Williams' Blue Five, Wilbur C. Sweatman's Orignal Jazz Band, Rosa Henderson, Angela Bassett,Bessie Smith, Fletcher Henderson, Darius Rucker, and Trixe Smith, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12412
      Rhino
    - Rhapsodies In Black: Music and Words from the Harlem Renaissance Disc Two: Testifyin' & Philosophyin' // Various Artists (Carl Hancock Rux, Cleo Brown, Paul Whiteman, Fred Longshaw, Perry Bradford's Jazz Phools, Ma Rainey, Sylvia Rhone, Paul Robeson, Duke Ellington & His Kentucky Club Orchestra, Thomas Morris & His Seven Hot Babies, Debbie Allen, Savoy Bearcats, Paul Whitman, Lonnie Johnson, Margret Johnson, Lou Rawls, Gladys Bently, Frankie Trumbauer, Johnny Dunn & His Band, and Alberta Hunter), 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12413
    - Rhapsodies In Black: Music and Words from the Harlem Renaissance Disc Three: Preachin' & Prayin' // Various Artists (Ice-T, Leadbelly, Victoria Spivey, Louis Armstrong, Lonnie Johnson & Blind Willie Dunn, Cecil Scott, Joshua Redman, Fats Waller, Bessie Smith, Jimmy Johnson, Gregory Hines, Fess Williams, McKinney's Cotton Pickers, Chocolate Dandies, Chuck D, Cab Calloway, Luis Russell, Ted Lewis, August Wilson, and Josh White), 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12414
    - "LP #2" // Blu Cantrell, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12415
    - The Experience // Yolanda Adams, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12416
    - Open Our Eyes // Earth, Wind, & Fire, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12417
      CD-R Reference Copy
    - Enter My Mind // Marlon Saunders, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12418
      Gram Cora Music
    - I Care 4 U // Aaliyah, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12419
      Blackground Records
    - If Only You Knew // Gina Thompson, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12420
      Promotional Copy - Unreleased Album
    - Two-Eleven // Toni Estes, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12421
      Priority Records
      50150
    - The Art Of A Woman // Athena Cage, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12422
      28395
    - Things In The Game Done Changed // Dave Hollister, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12423
    - LSG 2 // LSG, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12424
      32063
    - Same Girl // Trina Broussard, 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12425
    - That Girl // Ms. Toi, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12426
    - The Skinny // Slimm Calhoun, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12427
    - This Ain't a Game // Ray J, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12428
    - Nine Lives // AZ, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12429
    - The Life I Live // Torrey Carter, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12430
      62393-2
    - The Morning After // Deborah Cox, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12431
    - Bitter // Me'Shell Ndegeocello, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12432
    - The Mind of Gil Scott-Heron // Gil Scott-Heron, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12433
      TVT Records
    - The Magnet: Sountrack from The Motion Picture // Various Artists (Millie Jackson, Cunnie Williams, Talib Kweli, Gerald Alston, The Dells, Bruizza, Marlena Shaw, Issac Hayes, and Dennis Edwards), 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12434
      OmTown Music
      72438-50810-2-6
    - The Good Good: A 200 Black Compliation Presented by Planet E // Various Artists (Catalyst, MM Black, Pavel Kostiuk, Vanessa Freeman, Seji, Domu, Koniyuki, Titonton, Nubian Mindz, Somatik, Nu Era,and Da One Away, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12435
      Planet E Communications
    - So Plush // So Plush, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12436
    - Pleasures U Like // Jon B, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12437
    - Always Remember // Aaries, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12438
    - It's All About The Stragglers // Artful Dodger feat. Various Artists (Michelle Escoffery, Craig David,Lynn Eden, Lifford, MC Alistair, and Nadia), 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12439
      London/Sire Records
    - The Best of Busta Rhymes // Busta Rhymes, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12440
    - Olivia // Olivia, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12441
    - Request Line Dance Remixes // Zhane, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12442
    - Okayplayer True Notes Vol. 1 // Various Artists ( The Roots, Dilated Peoples, ?uestlove, Blackalicious, Hieroglyphics, Skillz, Jean Grae, RJD2, Aceyalone, Little Brother, and Madlib), 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12443
      Okayplayer Records
    - The Game // Chico DeBarge, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12444
    - Double Up // Mase, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12445
      Promotional Copy (?)
      Bad Boy Records
    - Verve Unmixed 3 // Various Artists, 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12446
      VERF01 403-2
    - Music // Erick Sermon, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12447
    - Lyricist Lounge 2 // Various Artists ( Nortorious B.I.G, Mos Def, Pharoache Monch, Q-Tip, Wordsworth, Beanie Sigel, Royce The 5'9, Ghostface Killah, Redman, Saukrates, Talib Kweli, Dead Prez, Kool G Rap, M.O.P., Big Noyd, Prodigy, Erick Sermon, Dialated Peoples, RZA, Macy Gray, Master Fuol, JT Money, and Pastor Troy, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12448
    - Get Down or Lay Down // Philly's Most Wanted, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12449
    - Trunk Funk Classics (1991-2000) // Brand New Heavies, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12450
    - Various Artists Rough Mixes // Various Artists (Olivia, Product G&B, and Jimmy Cozier), 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12451
    - Smooth Grooves: Steppers // Various Artists (William DeVaughn, Jennie Reynolds, The Jones Girls, Phil Collins, Down To The Bone, Blue Magic, The Ebonys, L.J Reynolds, Patti Austin, The Blackbyrds, Ray Obiedo featuring Peabo Bryson, and Michael Franks ), 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12452
    - Smooth Grooves: Live // Various Artists (Earth, Wind & Fire, Maze feat. Frankie Beverly, Average White Band, Billy Paul, Natalie Cole, The Dramatics, Rufus & Chaka Khan, Commodores, Donny Hathaway, The O'Jays, Teddy Pendagrass, and Marvin Gaye ), 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12453
    - Everything Is A Story // Rah Digga, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12454
      J Records/ Flipmode Records
    - Up Close and Personal // Angie Martinez, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12455
    - Didn't See Me Coming // Keith Sweat, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12456
    - Masterpiece Theatre // En Vogue, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12457
    - Just Raphael // Raphael Brown, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12458
      Promotional Copy - Unrelased Album?
    - This Is It // Celeda, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12459
      Advance Copy
      TWDPRP-11962
    - Lyric // Lyric, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12460
      CD-R Advance Copy - Unreleased Album
    - Music from The Motion Picture: Bad Company // Various Artists (Ali, St. Lunatics, D12, Gorilliaz, Outkast, Dub Pistols, Pretty Willie, Jaheim, Next, Jagged Edge, Blu Cantrell, Rama Duke,Tricky, Ko-La, and Supervision ), 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12461
      Hollywood Records
    - 3 Strikes Soundtrack // Various Artists ( Snoop Dogg, Boss Howg, Sauce Money, Solo & Kam, E40, Liquid Crew, Silk The Shocker, Niomesha, DJ Quik, Erick Sermon, Xzibit, C-Murder, Choclair, and Total, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12462
    - Kingdom Come Soundtrack // Various Artists ( Jill Scott, Carl Thomas, SOP Chorale, Shawn Stockmanm Trinitee 5:7, Deborah Cox, Tamar Braxton, 1NC, Bishop Ulmer, Crystal Lewis, AZ Yet, Kurt Carr, Tamela Mann, Yvette Williams, Kirk Franklin and Nu Nation), 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12463
      Gospo Centric
    - Forever // Puff Daddy, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12464
    - The Good life (FUBU album) // Various Artists (Nate Dogg, Nas, JS of 54th Platoon, The E.N.D, Ludacris, LL Cool J, Keith Murray, Mr. Cheeks, Amazin, Drunken Master, TL of 54th Platoon, Mac Don, Beenie Man, India.Arie, Super Cat, Phendi, Erick Sermon, Joe, Dawn Robinson, and Connie McKendrick, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12465
      Internal Copy
      Universal Records
    - Almost Famous // Lumidee, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12466
    - The Colored Section // Donnie, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12467
    - Star // 702, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12468
      Promtional Copy
    - Sttutered Melodies // Sttutered Melodies, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12469
      Not listed
    - On & On… // Jennifer Holiday, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12470
      CDK 9113
    - Petestumentals // Pete Rock, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12471
      BBE
      BBEBGCD002
    - Long Time Comin // Lil' Cease, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12472
    - Music From The Motion Picture: The Brothers // Various Artists (Eric Benet, Jermaine Dupri, ROC, Lil' Mo, RL, Jaheim, Gerald & Eddie Levert, Snoop Dogg, DL, Somethin For The People, Maze feat. Frankie Beverly, Lil' Johnny, Cassie, Duganz Da Don, AB, Dave Hollister, No Question, and Marcus Miller), 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12473
      Warner Bros
      2-48058
    - Black Coffee [Single] // All Saints, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12474
      London Records
    - Smoove [Mixtape] // DJ Neil Armstrong + Various Artists (Full Force, Sleepy Brown, New Edition, Soul 4 Real, Michael Jackson, Stevie Wonder, Fonda Rae, O'Jays, Al Green, Cheryl Lynn, Jay-Z, John Holt, Patrice Rushen, Minnie Riperton, Prince, Led Zeppelin, Pliers, Eugene Wilde, Groove Theory, El Debarge, Ready for the World, Janet Jackson, Art of Noise, Earth, Wind & Fire, Sade, Nina Sky, Lisa Lisa, Marvin Gaye, and Joe Bataan), 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12475
    - The Way You Love Me [Single] // Karyn White, 1988; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12476
      PRO-CD-3309
    - Told You So // Sparkle, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12477
    - Music From The Motion Picture: Big Momma's House // Various Artists( Da Brat, Missy Elliot, Jermaine Dupri, Nas, Monica, Kandi, Lil' Bow Wow, XSCAPE, Jagged Edge, Blaque, R.O.C., Kurupt, Phat Boss, Vita, Destiny's Child, La Tocha Scott, Chante Moore, Lil Jon & The Eastside Boyz, Devin, Marc Nelson, and Jessica, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12478
      So So Def/Sony
    - King Britt Presents Sylk 130 Re-members Only // King Brit + Various Artists (Allson Moyet, Mark Bell, Martin Fry, Kathy Sledge, Alma Horton, Twyla, Vikter Duplaix, Grover Washington, Jr., James Poyset, Capitol A, De La Soul, C-Knowledge, Cosmic Funk Orchestra), 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12479
      VUM Records
    - Music From The Motion Picture: Sparkle // Aretha Franklin, 2006; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12480
      Warner Bros/ Rhino
      31974-90-CD
    - J Records Urban Music Sampler Vol. 3 // Various Artists ( Monica, Busta Rhymes, Mariah Carey, The Flipmode Squad, Lyric, Tyrese, Joi Campbell, Heather Headley, Luther Vandross, Pretty Tony, Deborah Cox, Shells, Cassidy, Rah Digga, and Mario), 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12481
      J1DJ-21259-2
    - Bad Ass Kid // Malik Pendleton, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12482
    - Backdoor Daddy // Skillet Leroy & LaWanda, 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12483
      O.S.T. Grammofonpladen
    - Wild Light // Mount Sims, 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12484
      International DJ Gigolo Records
      6195681391
    - The Prize Collection - Booker T's Greatest Remixes // Booker T + Various Artists ( Camille Douglas, All Saints, Bizzi, Julliet Roberts, Da Mob, J. Brown, Soul II Soul, Brand New Heavies, Sounds of Blackness, Awesome, Connor Reeves, Kathy Wood,Jocelyn Enriquez, Agent 00, D'Influence, L2 Love, Mass Fusion, and Inner Souls., 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12485
      UK Import
      Azuli Records
      SOLIDCD 15
    - Rhona Compilation // Rhona, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12486
    - Black Gangster Original Soundtrack // Various Artists (Donald Goines Jr., Jay-Z, Ja Rule, DMX, Ghetto Mafia, Kasual, Jane Blaze, Mac Dre, Killa, Mysonne, Mac Mall, 50 Cent, Donell Jones, Freddie Foxxx, and Matx), 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12487
      Black Hand Entertainment
    - Experience: Jill Scott (Disc 2) // Jill Scott, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12488
      Hidden Beach Recordings
    - Love Songs // Grover Washington, Jr., 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12489
    - Cookie: The Anthropological Mix Tape // Meshell Ndegeocello, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12490
    - Raphael Saadiq as Ray Ray // Raphael Saadiq, 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12491
      Pookie Entertainment
    - Nivea // Nivea, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12492
    - R&B Jumpoff 19 // Big Mike & Big Stress, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12493
      PB&J
    - Jay-Z The Red Album // DJ Whoo Kid & Bach Logic, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12494
    - Live Evil (CD 1 of 2) // Miles Davis, 1997-04-28; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12495
      CK 65232
    - square window // Squarepusher, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12496
      Warp Records
      3WARPCD117
    - Official // Official, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12497
      Promotional Release?
    - Nervous Records NYC Fall/Winter 2000 Sampler // Various Artists, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12498
      Nervous NYC
    - Distance Sampler // Various Artists, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12499
      Distance
    - I'm Going All the Way [remixes] // The Sounds of Blackness, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12500
    - 702 [Rough mixes] // 702, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12501
    - Do You [CD single] // Heather B, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12502
    - Star Kitty's Revenge // Joi, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12503
    - hit 'em up style (oops!) remix featuring foxy brown // Blu Cantrell, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12504
    - "All Eyez On Me" Advance Music // Monica, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12505
    - Jon B. // Jon B., 2001; 1 Audio Disc